Ripped by BluCola
我们现在可以签字了吧
So, if we're ready for signature...?
You can absolutely guarantee it'll
be the final leg?
你们能绝对保证那是最后一程吗
（12年伦敦奥运会火炬传递）
当然 不然就算违约
Anything else would be in breach
of contract. Who's giving it to me?
谁会递给我
问得好 Phoebe 谁递给她
Excellent question, Phoebe! Who's
giving it to her? Er... Anthony?
厄  Anthony 告诉她
嗯
Erm...
Dame Kelly Holmes
Dame Kelly Holmes.
Ooh...
我不认识她
I don't know who she is.
She's
an Olympic athlete. I don't care.
- 她是奥运选手
- 我不在乎
我想要谁都行 不是吗 妈妈
爸爸是这么说的
I can have who I want, can't I,
Mummy? Daddy said! Well, darling...
- 那个 亲爱的
- 为什么我要的就是得不到
Why can't I ever have
anything I want? Well, it's...
- 嗯 这个
- 我们还有别的选择吗
Do we have any other choices?
Erm... Lord Coe.
- 厄 Coe议员
- 不行
No. Sir Ian Botham? No.
Sir Ian McKellen? No.
- Ian Botham爵士
- 不行
- Ian Mckellen爵士
Justin Bieber
Justin Bieber. Yes?
行吗
就他了
He'll be fine. Marvellous.
非常好
我们带来了一件复制品
这样Phoebe就有充分的时间准备了
We've brought along a replica
so that Phoebe has
plenty of time to prepare.
你从Justin手中接过来
So, you pick up from Justin,
then it's up the steps
走上台阶 就这么简单
and Bob's your uncle.
You're a very lucky girl.
姑娘 你很幸运
事实上这跟运气没啥关系
Actually, it has nothing to do
with luck. My Daddy is very,
very, very rich.
我爸爸非常
非常 非常有钱
她以她爸爸为豪
She's v proud of her father.
他说了 我能拥有我想要的一切
因为我是他的小公主
And he says I can have whatever
I want, because I'm his princess.
没错 你的确是
Yes, you are.
So, all we need now is
your sponsorship cheque. Of course.
现在只差你的赞助支票了
没问题
很好 这真是莫大的荣幸
Good. Well, it's been an
absolute pleasure. How exciting!
多激动人心啊
Lucinda一定会气疯的
Lucinda will be completely sick.
All she's doing is a stupid dance.
她只能去跳那只傻得要死的舞
She'll be one of hundreds,
but I'll be special.
她就是一群众演员
而我将是最特别的一个
没错 你会的 宝贝
Yes, you will, poppet.
那么接下来呢
So what happens now?
大概一周后 你就能收到所有的书面材料
All the paperwork will come through
in about a week or so - rehearsal
dates, VIP passes, details, etc.
包括彩排日期 贵宾通行证 各种细节等等
Just make sure you've marked
July 27th on your calendar.
你只需要确保你能记住7月27号这一天
毫无疑问
Abso-bloody-lutely!
Phoebe 说谢谢
Say thank you, Phoebe.
She's highly strung. V creative.
她一直神经紧绷
非常有创造力
噢 上帝会保佑她的
Oh, bless her.
如何
How'd it go? Like taking candy
from a baby. Ah-ha.
- 轻而易举
- 啊哈
真有趣 你总是会特别钟情于某些工作
It's funny how you enjoy some jobs
more than others.
那是这些人值得拥有
Some people are more deserving
than others.
- 所以干得更带劲
- 嗯 的确如此
Makes it all the sweeter.
Yes, it does. Mind you...
A hundred grand ain't to be sniffed
at. No. It's a lot of clothes.
主意 10万英镑可不容小觑
的确不容忽视
可以买很多衣服呢
实话说 反正他们钱多
To tell you the truth,
they had way too much money anyway.
仔细想想 我们跟侠盗罗宾汉有点儿像
I mean, when you think about it,
we're a bit like Robin Hood.
是啊 我们确实从富人那儿弄钱
Yeah, well,
we do take from the rich...
- 只不过不捐给穷人
- 我们拿来买衣服
Only instead of giving it
to the poor... We buy clothes.
- 还是挺低调的
- 的确
Which isn't quite as catchy.
No - but we look great.
但是我们就是酷毙了
<font color="#ffff00"-==http://www.1000fr.net==-
謦灵风软影视论坛荣誉出品
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
-=风软FRM字幕组=-
翻译：ElizabethZhao 钱呐 yang_yang 瑾
校对：画瞳
时间轴：破晓 阿拉蕾 一粒小麦
飞天侠盗 第八季 第1集
你会爱上奥林匹克的
You've gotta love the Olympics.
除了事实上他们把
Apart from the fact they're turning
the East End into
a chinless wonder's paradise.
伦敦东区变成了傻帽们的天堂
目前为止 我们已经卖出了
12个不存在的行政包厢
So far, we've sold
12 non-existent executive boxes
and three Olympic torch runs.
还有3个奥运火炬接力的名额
She was such a brat.
她真是讨人厌的小贱人
是啊 所以国家才会被搞成这样
Yeah... The way some people
bring up their children.
看看他们都怎么教孩子的
我在她这个年纪就只有
冰冻果子露和呼啦圈
All I had at her age was
a Sherbet Dib Dab and a hula hoop.
- 我每次都能轻松赢你
- 你吹牛的吧
I used to beat you hands down
every time. You bragging?
他们都叫我 水蛇腰肯尼迪
Snake Hips Kennedy, they used
to call me. He was such a girl.
实际上 这名字是他自己取的
他就是小弱受啊
不就是因为我总能打败你嘛
Only cos I used to beat you.
没错 因为你一直不把
我的呼啦圈还给我 这就是原因
Yes, because I couldn't
get it off you, that's why.
好了 孩子们
All right, children - we've made
100 grand, you can all have hoops.
我们刚有了10万
一人一打呼啦圈就不嫌多
你确定Albert这个年纪
还转得动呼啦圈吗 要转出人性命来的
Sure that's wise at Albert's age?
He might do himself a mischief. Oh?
我就来教你们小年轻一两手吧
Well, I could teach you youngsters
a thing or two.
你可以的 Albert
Yes, you could.
- 我算是明白你们了
- 咋了
I've worked something out about
you lot. You're like big kids. Yeah?
- 你们就是一群小毛孩子
- 是吗
你说有了10万所以一人一打
呼啦圈的时候就整明白了
I realised when you said you had
a 100 grand so everyone
could have hoops.
Who in their right mind,
if they had a 拢100,000,
哪个正常人会
想着用10万英镑去买呼啦圈
would spend it on hoops?
- Eddie 呼啦圈哪得罪你了
- 他可是呼啦圈代言人啊
He's hoopist. Could've had
a bad experience as a child.
- 也许是小时候有什么阴影了
- 是啊 挥之不去啊
Yeah, he got all tangled up...
Couldn't quite get the rhythm...
- 跟不上节奏什么的
- 我就是这个意思
看见没 你们就是一群
倒霉催的捣蛋鬼
See? You're like big kids,
messing about...
你是有什么要说吗 Ed
还只是在乱吼一通
Are you making a point here, Ed,
or just having a Northern rant?
There is a point, actually.
事实上 我是有事要说
One of you did this to Rushie!
你们当中某个人对Rushie干了什么
等等 你怎么知道是我们干的
Hang on.
How do you know it was one of us?
因为是昨晚发现的
那是只有你们在这儿
Cos it happened last night,
and you were the only ones in here.
- 好吧
- 好吧 所以呢 是谁干的
Right. Right? So? Who was it?
不管是谁干的 他肯定不会画画
看看这胡子画得多糟糕
Well, whoever it was can't draw,
cos his moustache is rubbish.
That's his real one.
那是他的真胡子
你们玷污了他 看看他
You've defiled him! Look at him!
可简直罪无可恕
It's not right, this!
This man was poetry in shorts.
他可是体育界的诗人
Summat funny, Michael?
有什么好笑的 Michael
不好笑 对不起
No. Sorry.
好吧 除非有人承认
否则你们就是黑名单
Eh? Barred?
- 诶
- 黑名单？
- 这有点过了吧 Ed
- 是啊 我们可是合伙人啊
That's a bit strong, innit Ed?
Especially as we're your partners.
你们平时取笑羞辱我就算了
I don't mind all the banter
and the general abuse,
but this is going too far!
但这个太过分了
好吧 我想最好有人承认
All right, I think someone
better own up.
What you looking at me for?
Well, you're the football nut.
- 你们看着我干嘛
- 你是铁杆球迷
- 喂喂 又不是所有球迷都是流氓
- 反正不是我
Oi, oi, we're not ALL hooligans.
Well, it wasn't me.
够了 你们全都上黑名单
直到我找出是谁干的
Right, well - you're barred, all
of you, till I find out who done it.
I mean it!
我没开玩笑
- 走吧
- 走吧 快点
Let's go. Well, go on. Come on.
- 黑名单
Barred? Barred!
说真的 伙计们
I'm serious, guys.
It's taken me years to teach Eddie
how to make a proper breakfast.
我花了好几年才教Eddie
做出像样的早餐
没错 更别说
失去我们的办公室了
Yes - not to mention
losing our office.
是啊 他那疯狂的利物浦球迷心
已经被点燃了
Yeah, well,
he's got that Scouse resolve.
He won't give up till one of us
admits it.
除非我们中有人承认了
否则他不会放弃的
所以 到底是谁干的
So go on. Who was it?
ALBERT COUGHS UNEASILY
I'm Spartacus. You?!
- 我有份
- 你
I did the ears.
I er...I did the glasses.
- 我画了耳朵
- 我 厄
我画了眼镜
And the beard?
那谁画的胡子
准备好了吗 看着
Ready for this? Watch.
THEY ALL GIGGLE AND MUTTER
(Hide the pen.)
看见没
See...?
嗯 这么做太幼稚了 不是吧
Well, that wasn't very grown-up,
was it? Albert started it.
Albert开的头
- 嘿 你个小八卦
- 噢 得了吧 那根本就...
Hey, you snitch.
Oh, come on, don't even start.
行了 够了
All right, that's enough,
that's enough.
我们晚点再担心Eddie吧
We can worry about Eddie later.
Albert's got a new mark. Oh, who?
- Albert找到了新目标
- 噢 谁
这个有点以公谋私了
It's er.. kind of personal.
Ash 能帮我一下吗
Ash, would you...help me out?
这是Dexter Gold 当然不是本名
This is Dexter Gold.
That's not his real name, he changed
it by deed poll four years ago.
四年前他用改名契改了名
- 他真名是什么
- Dexter Pratt
What's his real name? Dexter Pratt.
他建立了一个叫“黄金兑现金”的网站
Started up a "Gold Hard Cash"
website when the economy
went into turmoil
趁着大萧条的时候
发了点小财
and he made a small fortune.
与时俱进嘛
Classy guy.
路数就是有人手头紧了
People who needed a few extra pounds
saw his ads in the papers,
sent their jewellery in,
在报纸上看到他的广告
把珠宝交给他
and he conned them by paying out
a fraction of what it was worth.
他骗他们说那只值
实际价值的一小部分
我是这样发现他的
That is how I found him.
INDISTINCT CHATTER
失陪一下
Excuse me for just for a moment.
Sorry.
夫人
Madam?
Vivienne Marchant的丈夫
三年前去世了
'Vivienne Marchant hit hard times
之后她的日子就很艰难
'when her husband died
three years ago.'
- 最糟的是 我觉得自己太傻了
- 噢 不会 不是的
The worst thing is,
I feel so stupid.
Oh, no, no.
以前只要是报纸上
There was a time, when if it
was in a newspaper written in
black and white, it was true!
白纸黑字写的 那就不会有假
- 美好的岁月啊
- George肯定会很生气
Better days.
My George would be furious.
他一定会冲过去给他点教训
He'd have gone round there,
given him what for.
I'm sure he would.
- 我相信
- 我也试过了
I tried! He just laughed at me.
他却取笑我
Said the conditions were
written down.
说是条件都下笔成书了
无疑是用小号字体写的
In small print, no doubt.
Albert 你能帮我真是太好了
It's really good of you to help me,
Albert.
亲爱的 这年头你一定要非常小心
You can't be too careful who you
trust these days, my dear.
这世界变了
The world isn't what it was.
After all, you only met me, what,
你看 我们也只认识了三天
three days ago?
I could be a con-man too.
我也可能是个骗子啊
噢 别傻了
Oh, don't be so daft!
DOG GROWLS QUIETLY
她给那杂种送去了这些 听着
She sent this piece of filth -
listen to this -
一对24K金戒指 一个钻石胸针
two 24 carat gold rings,
a diamond brooch.
60 years of memories.
60年的记忆啊
他给了她28.5英镑
He sent her back 拢28.50.
- 混蛋 - 我们要是不把这贱人
骗的每一分钱都讨回来
Bastard. If we don't take this bloke
for every penny he's got,
你去就扇他耳巴子当锻炼
I'll smack him in the mouth
just for fun.
别担心 Ash 我们会搞定他的
Don't worry, Ash, he'll receive
our full attention.
啊 是的 不过有点小问题
Ah, yes,
there is a bit of a problem.
Isn't there always?
不总会有问题吗
Michael?
Michael
我们查了一下
We checked him out and his
Gold Hard Cash business, it seems,
似乎他的黄金兑现金业务
is just a sideline.
只是他的副业
他与2008年发生在Gatwick的
He was connected to the gold bullion
robbery at Gatwick in 2008
还有去年Tottenham仓库的
金块抢劫案都有关系
and the Tottenham warehouse
gold heist last year. He's a fence?
他是销赃人？
他是被盗金块销赃的中间人
He's a middle man
for stolen gold bullion.
他利用他的黄金兑现金业务
He uses his Gold Hard Cash
business as a cover to melt it down
and sell it on.
做掩护 把金块熔掉 然后出售
这点会影响他的骗子身份吗
What difference does it make if he's
a crook? Well, he's not just
a crook, he's one of the chaps.
他不仅是骗子 他还是金主之一
* When the pimp's in the *
* Crib drop it like it's hot *
# When the pimp's in the crib
Drop it like it's hot
* Drop it like it's hot *
# Drop it like it's hot
* When the pigs try to give it you *
# When the pigs try to give it you
* Park it like it's hot *
# Park it like it's hot
* If a ... get a attitude *
# If a ... get a attitude
* Pop it like it's hot *
# Pop it like it's hot
Pop it like it's hot
# Pop it like it's hot... #
So, because of the circles
所以考虑到他混迹的圈子
he mixes in, we don't want him
coming after us.
我们不希望他盯上我们
Or worse, telling one
of his gangster friends
或者更糟糕的是
他告诉某个黑帮的朋友
他被骗了 他会给他们更高的报酬
he's been conned and offering them a
better deal if they take care of us.
只要他们搞定我们
所以我们如果接手
So, if we do this, we need to
close it off when we're done.
我们就得结束的干干净净的
同意吧
Agreed? Yeah. Yeah.
- 没问题
- 行
很好 那我们开始吧
Good. Then let's find a way in.
搞定了
Bish bosh, job's a good 'un.
写支票吧 寄到
Write the cheque, send it to
Number One, Winners Street,
Daddy's bringing home the bacon.
Winners大街1号 一切就OK了
我说了是24K
When I said this deal was 24 carat,
was I right or was I wrong? Hang on.
没说错吧 等等
要聊天 下班后
Talk on your own time.
你敢再碰一下那手机
我就用它爆你的菊花
You touch that bleedin' phone again
and I'll shove it up your jacksy.
我没说错吧
So was I right or wrong?
别 别只是笑嘻嘻敷衍我嘛 Peter
直接了当
No, don't just laugh and say "Yeah,"
Peter, actually say the words...
我说得对不对
Was I right or wrong?
就是嘛 钱还没出去事就搞定了
Exactly, you get your deal sorted
out before you spend your money.
明白了不
Capiche?
我们是中间人 不是投资者
We're middle men not investors,
我们能成 他们也就成 明白吗
when we get the deal,
they get the deal, OK?
好了滚吧 听我的话
Now sod off and next time
listen to me instead of
别相信你浪费了五年时间
读的那个没用的商学位
that poxy business degree you wasted
five years of your life on.
Shania 请你的大屁股移驾过来
Shania, get your arse over here.
我的杯子是空的
Me mug's empty.
Excuse me?
什么意思
我跟你说什么来着
茶 我进来就要喝
What have I told you?
Mug of tea, the minute I get in.
他喜欢电影
Well, he likes his movies.
- 电影?
- 对 我刚黑进了他的网络DVD租赁账户
Movies? I hacked into
his online DVD rentals account.
- 他三周租了27部电影
- A片?
He's got 27 films in three weeks.
Porn?
最诡异的是 不是A片
看样子都是些战争片
Strangely enough, no, they all look
like war films. War? Yeah.
- 战争?
- 对 这意味着什么
- 他喜欢看人被打中被炸飞
- 真棒
What does that say about him?
That he likes to watch people
being shot and blown up. Nice.
如果他喜欢战争电影...
If he likes war movies...
What about this?
这个如何
看样子卡扎菲在美国佬对他乱枪扫射时
It looks like Gadaffi was trying to
ship out some of his goodies
正想把他的一些财产转移
while the Yanks took pot shots
at him and a couple of truck loads
went missing.
几车货失踪了
其中一车被认为载有金条
One of which was thought to be
gold bullion.
他们认为是游击队干的
They think it's a rogue army unit.
我们就用这个做背景?
So we use this as our back story?
干嘛不呢 这也符合他的个性
Why not? It fits his personality.
这是真事 所以经得起调查
It's true, so it'll check out,
也省了我们特地设套引他入局
and it saves time having to set
something up from scratch.
- 嗨
- 你好
Hi. How you doing?
- 给你
- 谢了 再见
There you go. Thanks, bye. Cheers.
再见
真的 他性别歧视
Honestly, he is so sexist,
apparently every woman in flat shoes
is a lesbian.
他显然认为穿平底鞋的都是蕾丝边
No wonder he hasn't got
a girlfriend.
难怪他没有女朋友
问题是 Baz
分销货物对我们没好处
Thing is, Baz,
splitting up consignments
ain't doing us any favours, we need
someone who can take the lot.
我们需要个能吞下大头的
我待会要见个德国老鬼
I'm seeing this German geezer
later on,
他说我们手头有的他都能收了
he says he can take
whatever we've got.
我不是要耍花样
I ain't trying to pull a fast one,
but a troy ounce of gold was 875
quid when I woke up this morning.
但目前一金衡盎司黄金
市值875英镑
Now, unless you know
something I don't,
除非你知道些有的没的
不然为什么我的价要低于这个数呢
why would I get less than that?
你国内收的我们可以给875镑
We'll give you 875
for your domestic business,
但我们有消息
but we are aware that sometimes
your sources are not always...
有时你的货源并不...
合法?
legitimate?
如果你想跟我们合作
So, if you want to use us
又不想我们过问"这东西打哪儿来"
but you don't want us to ask,
"Where is it coming from?"
那我们就要便宜点了 对吧
then we like to pay
a little less, ja?
好 好
Yeah, yeah.
那么...你们能吃进多少货
So, uh...how much can you take?
没有上限
We have no upper limit.
- 付费方式呢
- 你喜欢哪种
And payment?
What's your preference?
现金
Cash.
德国反洗钱法案
The money laundering laws
are very stringent in Germany.
管得很严
- 汇票或直接转账
- 可以
Bankers draft or direct transfers.
Agreed.
我们直接转账的最高额度是2百万欧元
We have a 2m euro ceiling
on direct transfers.
看样子你是找到英国的供货商了
Looks like you've found
your UK supplier.
你看 靠熔掉那些感觉自己
被骗的老家伙送上门的首饰
You see, melting down trinkets sent
in by wrinklies feeling the pinch
我可建不起新泳池 对吧 Barry
这可是大实话
ain't going to build my new pool,
is it, Barry? Let's be honest.
商人就要不遗余力地榨取利润...
And the dealers are squeezing
all the margins, so...
the Krauts have agreed
to take whatever we can supply,
德国佬已经说了他照单全收
没上限
no upper limit.
咣当打开收银机 收下零钱
So, bish bosh, open up the till,
keep the change.
那我们从何入手呢 老板
So, when do we start, boss?
我跟他说下周末会给他第一批货
I told him I'd send him his first
shipment at the end of next week.
有几个小子在筹划大买卖
There's a couple of the lads
planning jobs.
A cargo terminal at Stansted
and an Arab bank in Kensington.
Stansted的一个货运码头
还有Kensington一家阿拉伯银行
但还得等几周 要是金子不够
But they're a few weeks away,
so, if there's no hooky gold about,
那就多打些平面广告
let's get a few more
press ads running.
编织杂志 登些会吓到傻帽们的
Knitting magazines, something
to terrify the bingo squad,
"经济衰退 油价飞涨"
"Recession to bite deep,
fuel prices to soar.
"羊毛衫和蓝色染发剂的价格即将冲顶"
"The cost of cardigans and blue
rinses to go through the roof.
"如果你暖气都开不了了 婚戒何用"
"What use is your wedding ring
if you can't turn the heating on?"
Maybe do a special offer for widows!
也许可以给寡妇特价
我喜欢你这手 Baz
I like what you did there, Baz.
从家庭主妇入手
Yeah. And then let's start with
the housewives, make 'em feel guilty
让她们对自己守着黄金却
没让孩子玩上最新的电子游戏
about their kids
not having the latest video games
而心怀愧疚
while they're still
dripping in gold.
弄些孩子们哭的照片
Do some photos of kids...crying.
Right, get on with it!
I'm on it, boss!
- 对吧 快去办
- 这就去 老板!
大踏步前进 Baz
Big push, Baz, OK?
Shania
Shania?
Sean 有什么收获
Sean, what have you got?
根据他助理的说法 他单身
Well, according to his PA,
he's single,
通常状态是周旋于几个女朋友之间
in between girlfriends,
which is his usual state,
不是任何俱乐部的成员 只喝香槟
he's not a member of any clubs,
only drinks champagne,
尤好宝林歇 讨厌狗
preferably Bollinger, hates dogs,
women in flat shoes
穿平底鞋的女人和黄油布丁
and bread-and-butter pudding.
And his lucky number's five.
幸运数字是5
支持热刺 从不去现场看球
So... Supports Tottenham,
never goes to live matches,
最喜欢的歌星是Michael Buble
Shirley Bassey和麦当娜
his favourite singers are Michael
Buble, Shirley Bassey and Madonna.
最喜欢的电影是拯救大兵瑞恩
His favourite film
is Saving Private Ryan.
周末会玩彩弹枪
Plays paintball on the weekend.
最喜欢的颜色是金色
Favourite colour's gold.
On the rare occasion
极少数情形下会参加化妆舞会
会装扮成金手指
he does go to a fancy dress party
he goes as Auric Goldfinger,
007里面的人物 但谁都看不出来
the bloke from the Bond film,
but no-one ever knows who he is.
他还有只叫Goldie的鹦鹉
Oh, and he's got a parrot
named Goldie.
好吧 Emma?
OK. Emma? He's listed as a director
of 11 companies, all gold-related,
他是11家公司的董事
都是做黄金生意的
总营业额达三百万英镑
with a combined turnover of 拢3m,
我想他算是过了贫困线了
so, I think we can say
he's above the poverty line.
道具?
一切就绪 随时可以开始
Props?
Everything's in place, ready to go.
我们的饵呢
And what about our bait?
饵嘛...
Ah, our bait...
...看着有点像...
..looks a little something like...
...这样
..this.
Ooh...
是真的吗
Wow. Is that real?
Oh, yes.
- 对
- 值差不多三万二
32 grand's worth, give or take.
It's rented, so it has to go back
in one piece when we're done.
是租的 搞定后得完璧归赵
这该能引起他注意了
That should get his attention.
他四点在郊区有个会面
Oh... He's got a four o'clock
meeting out in the sticks.
让我们请君入瓮吧
Then let's bring him in.
MUSIC BLARES
HE SINGS TUNELESSLY
THUD OF AN IMPACT
Hngh...?!
- 你想死吗
- 不想
Do you want to die? No.
15秒内 会有六个人从林子里出来
In about 15 seconds, six blokes
are going to come out of the woods.
他们会先杀了我 在杀你取乐
They'll kill me first,
then shoot you just for fun.
进车里去 开车
So, get in the car and drive.
快
Now!
他上车了
He's in.
They jumped me on the way back
from their so-called dealers.
他们在我见了所谓的经销商后
回去的路上埋伏我
肯定是个圈套
It must have been a setup.
不 不 我搭了辆便车
No, no, no, I flagged a ride.
不 他只是一般人 没事的
No, he's a civilian, it's all right.
我一小时内回去 你放心吧
I'll be back in an hour,
you just sit tight.
听着 很抱歉把你拖进来
OK, look, I'm sorry
to drag you into this,
只是我走投无路了
你又恰好在那出现
but I was up shit creek
and you just happened to be there.
你救我一命
You saved my life.
我欠你的
I owe you one.
Who was after you?
是谁在追杀你
一群贪婪的混蛋
Greedy bastards, that's who.
你救了我 这需要勇气
But you got me out and that takes
guts. You ever been in the forces?
你当过兵吗
没有 我想过加入自卫队
No. I thought about the TA once.
Oh, you should do it. Yeah? Yeah.
- 你该去试试
- 是吗
嗯
Is that what I think it was?
那东西是我以为的东西吗
是又怎样
What if it was?
我听到你讲电话了 经销商什么的
I heard you on the phone,
about the dealer.
- 你是要给我惹麻烦吗 小子
- 不 不
Am I going to have trouble
with you, son? No, no.
事实上 我就是干这个的
The thing is, that's what I do.
- 什么
- 我是个黄金经销商
What?
I'm a gold dealer.
是啊 是啊 当然了
Yeah, yeah, course you are.
听着 谢谢你载我 打搅之处请原谅
Listen, thanks for the ride,
sorry for the inconvenience.
不 不 听着 这是我的名片
No! No, look, look. Here's my card.
如果你有东西要出手
我可以找到买家
If you got something to sell,
I can find a buyer.
你觉得奏效了吗
You think it worked?
所谓贪婪嘛
Well, that's the thing about greed.
It's very predictable.
就是非常容易预知
很好
Great.
Sean 明早你能把我们弄进他办公室吗
Sean, can you get us into
his offices tomorrow morning?
可以 我给Shania打个电话
她是我最新密友
Yeah, I'll call Shania,
my new best friend.
Look, we've got to do something
about Eddie. Yeah, I said that.
听着 Eddie那边我们得想想办法
嗯 我也那么说来着
来了
There we go. Enjoy.
慢用
- Eddie那边我们得想想办法
- 我有个主意
We need to do something about Eddie.
I have an idea. Oh, yeah?
- 是吗
- 我要求助场外观众
I'm going to call in a favour.
PHONE RINGS
你好 Eddie酒吧
Hello, Eddie's bar.
- 我是Ian Rush
- 什么
It's Ian Rush here. 'What?'
拜托 真是可悲 你声音根本不像他
Do me a favour, that's pathetic.
You don't even sound like him.
听着 我不知道你哪位
但你告诉那帮家伙
Hey, listen, I don't know who
you are, but you can tell that lot
我不像他们想的那么蠢 懂吗 你他...
that I'm not as stupid as they
think I am, all right? Ya f...
好办法 可惜他不信我们
Nice try, but he didn't believe us.
OK. Albert, Emma.
See if you can work on him.
好吧 Albert Emma
看你们能不能搞定他
为什么是我 我可没在
他的足球英雄照片上画耳朵
Hey, why me? I didn't draw ears
on his football hero!
- 他对你耳朵比较软
- 我可不会为让Ash吃上热食就跟他上床
He's got a soft spot for you.
I'm not sleeping with him
just so Ash can have a fry up.
- 那是你的问题了 Ems 你真自私
- 不好笑
That's your trouble, Ems.
You're selfish. Not funny.
就告诉他是Albert干的 他会道歉 完了
Just tell him it was Albert.
He can apologise, end of.
- 为什么是我
- 那就Mickey
Oh, but why me? Oh, Mickey then.
不能告诉他是Mickey
因为他会跟Mickey没完没了
We won't tell him it was Mickey, cos
he'll make Mickey's life a misery.
- Albert 就说是Sean
- 慢着!
Hang on! Sean, you're the youngest.
Sean 这里你最小
如果你们告发我 我就拖你们俩下水
Well, if you grass me up,
I'm taking you all down with me.
Aren't we forgetting something here?
It is Eddie we're talking about.
我们是不是忘了什么了
我们说的可是Eddie
Ash说得对 我是在让两个顶级骗子
Ash is right, I'm sending
two premier league grifters
对付一个酒保 大炮打蚊子
to deal with one barman,
it shouldn't be a contest.
- 不过他实在是倔
- 你会有办法的
He's really stubborn, though.
You'll think of something.
最好用黄铜
Brass may be your best bet.
不便宜 但熔化铸成砖后能以假乱真
It won't be cheap
but it will look the part
once it's melted down
and moulded into blocks.
开个价吧 Arnie
Well, give us a ball park, Arnie.
我能收回的话五千 否则一万
Five grand if I get it back,
ten if I don't. Done.
成交
好 那这个呢
OK. What about this?
- 你要怎样
- 改一个戳
What do you need?
A different seal on it.
那我得先熔掉它
Well, I'll have to melt it down
so I can stamp it.
你能办好吗
Can you do that?
只要是金属做的 Mickey
我就能搞定
If it's made of metal, Mickey,
I can do anything.
ASH SNIGGERS
金属Mickey?
(也是米老鼠的全名)
Metal Mickey?
算了
Never mind.
- 你想印上什么
- 这个
What seal do you need on it?
This one.
八点半见
We'll see you at 8.30.
I don't believe you. It's true.
You wouldn't do that, Albert,
- 我不信
- 真的
不会是你干得 Albert 你是在保护某人
you're just protecting someone.
Eddie!
Eddie! 既然你不信
为什么让我们中的谁站出来道歉
Why ask one of us to apologise if,
when we do, you don't believe us?
- 你们只是把我当傻瓜
- 没有
You're just taking me for a mug.
No, we're not.
- 那你们叫来给我打电话的谁呢
- 谁
What about the fella
you got to phone up?
- 那个假装Ian Rush的家伙
- 他真的是Ian Rush
The one pretending to be Ian Rush?
No, it actually was Ian Rush.
又来了 拿我当白痴
You're doing it again, treating me
like an idiot. You're impossible!
Eddie 你真是不可理喻
- 你们继续禁止入内
- 我跟你上床能了结吗
And you're barred.
What if I slept with you?
- 不能
- 什么
No. What?!
Sorry, I panicked just then,
I meant to say yeah. Eddie!
抱歉 刚刚吓到了 我想说可以的
Eddie!
听着 我知道是他干的
在他亲自过来道歉
Listen, I know he did it
and until he comes here in person,
并在证人前承认
apologises and says in front
of witnesses that Liverpool FC
利物浦比西汉姆要强之前
你们都继续留在黑名单上
are better than West Ham,
then you're staying barred.
不可能 我是说
不要脸 又不是我干的
It's not happening.
I mean, the flaming cheek of it,
and I never did it.
他认为是你干的 没办法说服他
He's convinced it was you and
there's no persuading him otherwise.
Come on, Ash, man up.
拜托 Ash 拿出点男子气概来
为大伙牺牲一下
Take one for the team.
不
No.
- 就花个20秒 能有多难
- 不是我干的
It takes 20 seconds,
how hard can it be? I ain't done it.
- 你俩一样倔
- 我什么也没干
You are as stubborn as each other.
I didn't do anything!
想想Eddie做的早餐
Think of Eddie's breakfast.
Yeah, he's finally got
his fried bread right.
他终于做对炸面包了
酥脆的外皮 湿润的内里
Crunchy crust,
a bit soggy in the middle.
不要
No.
我宁可挨饿
I'd rather starve.
谢谢
Thanks.
His diary's full
but he's got a gap in ten minutes...
他行程排满了
但十分钟后有个空...
好
Right.
- 早上好
- 准备好了?
Morning.
We set?
如果你弄丢了 就从你工资里扣
Yeah, if you lose it,
I'm stopping it out your wages.
祝我好运吧
Wish me luck.
你昨天把这个给了我朋友
You gave this to a friend of mine
yesterday.
* Oh it feels so good *
# Oh, it feels so good
* To have you by my side on a sunday morning *
# To have you by my side
on a Sunday morning
* Let's work together, baby *
# Let's work together, baby, yeah. #
* Yeah *
Shania! Get yourself
a cup of tea, love.
Shania! 自个喝茶去 宝贝儿
You were kind enough
to give him a lift.
多谢你昨天载他一程
那您来这里有何贵干呢
So what's on your mind?
哦 我想你知道我来这的原因吧
Oh, I think you know why I'm here.
Why don't you spell it out for me?
你为何不亲口说出来呢
我手头有些货 想找个买家
We have some merchandise. We're
having trouble finding a buyer.
- 好吧 我听说了
- 即便如此 你也得出个体面的价格
Yeah, so I heard.
That doesn't mean you won't have
to pay a decent price.
You'll have to let the dog
see the rabbit first.
总得让我先见见货吧
利比亚?
Libyan? Problem?
- 有问题么
- 当然没有
Not for me.
这么说你感兴趣 是吧
So you're interested, then?
It's what I do. I'm a middle man.
我就是干这行的 我是个中间人
我找到交易双方
彼此有对方想要的东西
I find two parties, each wanting
something the other has,
却又联系不上...
and no way of coming together...
所以 实际上 我就是个提供便利的人
So, really, I'm a facilitator.
The bottom line is, I can find a
buyer for that with one phone call.
但底线是 我一个电话就能找到买家
很好
Good. As long as you and your
boyfriend understand three things.
但是有三件事
你男朋友必须得明白
我猜他是你男朋友 没错吧
I'm assuming he is your boyfriend?
Yes, he is.
恩 没错
猜到了
That's what I thought.
Where was I? Three things?
- 说到哪儿了
- 三件事
首先 我不是个暴徒
Yeah, right. I'm not a mug,
apart from the Libyan stamp,
除了那个利比亚印章之外
昨天发生的事情告诉我
金条肯定有缺陷 还有...
all that drama yesterday tells me
it's obviously nicked, and, er...
利比亚财产被盗
I read the newspapers
like everybody else...
我也看了报纸...
I know where this has come from,
我知道金条从何而来
所以价格嘛 也会有所反映
so the price I pay will have
to reflect that.
Second.
第二点
我会从你那收20%的中介费
My commission for negotiating this
deal is 20% at your end,
non-negotiable.
这点没得商量的
第三呢
And third?
要是你敢晃点我
If you so much as think
about turning me over,
我认识些人 他们会找到你
让你受尽人间之苦
I know people who can track
you down and hurt you
so much you'll be begging them
to finish you off.
到时候 你会希望他们一枪结果了你
I'll pass it on.
我会传达的
我们商量好价格之后
通知我那些金条的交易细节
Once we've agreed a price, just
let us know where they need to go.
你是说不止一块吗
You mean there's more than one?
是的
Yes.
那...到底有多少呢
So...
how many we talking about exactly?
A hundred.
100个
A hundred! All the same as that one?
100个! 都跟这个一模一样的?
不少嘛
You mean you've got the whole lot?
You trying to tell me it was you...
- 如果你是想说...
- 这些对你来说太多了...
If this is too big for you...
哪里...
Oh, no... It might take more than
one phone call that's all...
只是不止要一个电话了嘛...
我能验验货吗
Can I see them? I don't know.
不知道
My contacts don't like being
pissed about. If I don't see the
goods, I don't pick up the phone.
我的客户可不想被爽约
所以如果我不见货
我是不会打电话的
你决定吧
It's your choice.
就在我朋友昨天下车的地方
The place where you
dropped our mutual friend,
今天下午两点
two o'clock this afternoon.
额滴神
Holy shit.
上钩了
I think we have a nibble.
Shania
Shania!
给Heinz Zimmerman拨电话
Get Heinz Zimmerman on the phone.
Then put the kettle on.
然后把水烧上
经得住吗
Will it stand up?
- 经得住什么
- 验货
To what?
- 没问题
- 那就好
Inspection. 100%. Good.
只要在6尺开外
As long as you don't get
within six feet.
这可不是小钱 Heinz
我们说的可是100公斤的24K纯金啊
This aint chicken feed, Heinz,
we're talking 100 kilos of 24 carat,
this is a serious shipment.
- 这可不是开玩笑的
- 什么时候能准备好
When's it ready?
我们要先把它熔了
重新盖印章 但我能...
Well, we'll need to melt it down
and restamp, but I can...
I can do the paperwork...
the question is can you handle it?
手续的问题就交给我了
但问题是你能吃进吗
你别光说不练呢
You talk the talk buddy,
it's time to walk the walk.
值三百万呢 干还是不干
There's three mill's worth here,
are you in or are you out?
好吧 我要了
'OK we have a deal, I'll be there.'
好咧 保持联系
Good call, be in touch.
* Yo mic check mic check *
# Yo, mic check, mic check
# Yeah here you go
Nah, here, over here
* Yeah here you go nah here over here *
* Yeah I heard he got that hot new thing *
# Yeah, I heard he got
that hot new thing
* Oh la la la yeah oh yeah yeah turn it over *
# Oh-la-la-la. Yeah oh, yeah, yeah
Turn it over. #
嗨 宝贝儿
别动 不然我打爆你的头 听到了吗
All right, babes?
Don't move or I'm gonna blow
your brains out, do you hear me?
伦敦又不是只有Eddie这一个酒吧
Eddie's isn't the only bar
in London.
或许我们就换一家好了
Maybe we should just find
somewhere else?
不不 我们会有办法解决的
No, no, we'll find a way to sort it.
抱歉 但是我们不能暴露地点
Sorry about that,
but we can't disclose our location.
英国军方派了一个特遣队抓我们
The British army have sent
a special ops unit to find us.
那是当然
Oh, well, fair enough then!
别介意 他对谁都不放心
Oh, don't mind him.
He's just not the trusting type.
You all right then?
你还好吧
So, you think you can get us a deal?
你真能帮我们做成这笔买卖吗
当然啦 但也不容易
我之前跟你女友说啦
Yes, I do.
But it won't be easy,
as I told your lady friend here.
- 多少钱
- 很难说
How much? Well, that's hard to say.
- 我跟你说什么来着
- 放松
What was I telling you? Relax.
There's 100 bars.
总共有100个
我查了下 每个价值3万
I looked it up, they're worth
about 30 grand each.
If you buy 'em from
the Bank of England, yeah, maybe...
如果你从英格兰银行买的话 是没错...
But you won't get anything near
that, not for a shipment like this.
可你想这么来可拿不到半毛钱
尤其是这种货
没有法律文件 金条就动不了 你得...
You can't move gold on without
paperwork. You need to, er,
先把它熔了 换个身份 再进入市场
melt it down, give it
a new identity, feed it back
into the system.
这都要花时间 还有钱
That takes time and money.
你想说这不容易是吗
You talking to us
about it not being easy?
三个月前 在利比亚
我们刚完一次作战任务
Three months ago, we'd just done
a black ops stint in Libya,
躲着美国佬的巡航导弹
还有阿帕奇武装直升机
dodging yank cruise missiles
and Apache gun ships,
smuggling rebel supporters out of
Tripoli before Gaddafi got to them.
在卡扎菲找到叛军之前
把他们偷送出的黎波里
卡扎菲让自己的秘密警察
Gaddafi got his secret police
to move his stash of goodies
在叛军到来之前 把东西都运走了
before the rebels arrived.
艺术品 现金 还有金子
Artwork, cash... Gold.
他死之后 我们在出的黎波里的路上
截获了运金条的车
He died, we caught the gold truck
on the road out of Tripoli.
我们把它洗劫一空
And we...relieved them of it.
现在 我们拼死跨越大半个非洲
Now we have not fought our way
across half of Africa,
carrying 100 kilos in gold bars and
then smuggled them into the UK,
把100公斤金条偷运进英国
不是为了让你个一脸贱样的
平民渣子给痛宰的
just so some smarmy scumbag civilian
can try to rip us off.
do you get me?
- 听明白了吗
- 退后 下士
Back off, Corporal.
HE LAUGHS
遵命 长官
Yes, sir.
HE CONTINUES LAUGHING
到底多少
How much?
I can get you half a million,
transferred into any account,
anywhere in the world in 20 seconds.
50万 转至任意账户
世界各地 20秒之内到帐
我情愿一枪毙了他
I'd rather shoot him where he
stands. You want to spend another
two weeks in here!?
你还想在这里再呆两周吗
我们已经被骗了两次了
We've been screwed over twice now.
这个价可不低了 我保证
You won't get a better price,
I guarantee it. He's playing us.
他耍我们呢
50万英镑可不是个小数目
Half a million pounds
is a lot of money.
50万不包括佣金怎样
What about half a million,
but no commission?
你转手时想赚多少随你便
Yeah? I say we negotiate.
- 佣金没得商量
- 是吗 我就要商量
好吧
All right! OK!
Forget the commission. Heart of
gold, that's my trouble. When?
那就不算佣金了 谁让我这么善良呢
时间呢
I need to verify the shipment first.
我得先验下货
要拿块样品 测纯度
I mean a sample, check the purity.
What else?
还有呢
如果一切顺利 24小时内就能搞定
Well, if it all checks out, I can
get this done in 24 hours.
Bish bosh!
就给你24个小时
24 hours.
- 怎么样
- 我滴妈 老板
Well?
Bloody hell, boss.
- 绝对极品 24K的
- 还有呢
It's top end, 24 carat. And?
是利比亚政府的印章 如假包换
Well, it's Libyan government seal,
it's about as kosher as it gets.
What's it worth?
价值多少
金价早上又涨了点 所以...
Gold price this morning was up a
bit, so... Just about 拢33,500?
大概是33,500
So 100 bars...?
那100个...
330万 不算零头
Three million,
three hundred thousand, and change.
Hmm.
吃滴来了
Grub's up. Great!
太好了
刚刚来电话 明天一切就绪
The mark just called, everything's
set up for tomorrow. We're just
running through a few things.
有几件事我们还得再商量一下
- 好的 Albert的两份鳕鱼
- 谢谢
Oh, right. Er, two cod, Albert.
Thank you. And one for Mickey.
Mickey一份
我的派 Ems的黑线鳕
Pie for me, haddock for Ems...
..And a saveloy for Sean. Saveloy!
还有Sean的五香辣味腊肠
五香辣味腊肠!
- 他啥时打的电话
- 大概20分钟以前
So, when did he phone?
About 20 minutes ago.
It'll be a pleasure to
take his money.
拿他钱真让我开心
如果成功的话
Albert想拿一份给Vivienne
If this works, Albert was thinking
of giving some money to Vivienne,
让她去坐个游轮什么的
you know, maybe send her on a cruise
or something. Great idea.
好主意
别忘了 Eddie的事还没解决呢
Don't forget, we've still got to
sort Eddie out as well. Yes, we do.
可不是嘛
我先申明 我可不会为
莫须有的事情道歉
I'm not apologising for something
I didn't do.
当然不用 没人让你去
No, of course not, no-one would
expect you to. Sean had an idea.
Sean有个主意
Mm, I mean, he wouldn't believe me
that it was Albert,
他不相信是Albert做的
但我想 如果我再努努力
能让他相信是我干的
but I reckon, if I try hard enough,
I can convince him it was me.
What, you'd hold your hand up?
咋 你要认错了吗
是啊 如果只有这个办法 我万死不辞啦
Yeah, if that's what it takes to fix
it then that's what I have to do.
说得好 Sean
Well, I think that's brilliant,
Sean.
嗯嗯
Yeah. Yeah, it is. Only thing is,
I'm not sure what to say to him.
唯一的问题是 我不知该跟他说什么好
- 就说你很抱歉在他的照片上乱画
- 这样就行
Just say sorry for scribbling
on his photo. Yeah, fine.
不不不 这可不够
那可是Ian Rush啊
No, no, no, no, it was more
than that, it was Ian Rush.
对利物浦球迷来说
他就是足球皇室成员
He's football royalty for Scousers.
No, you've got to say something
like, erm...
你应该说...
很抱歉弄脏了有史以来
最伟大足球运动员的照片
I'm sorry for defacing the
photograph of the greatest
footballer who ever lived.
有点过啊
Sounds a bit over the top.
跟你说 他高兴还来不及呢
Yeah, well he's obsessed,
I'm telling you.
其他的呢
What about the other thing, though?
That he wants us to say that
Liverpool is better than West Ham?
他想让我们承认利物浦
比西汉姆好怎么办
不会的啦 那只是针对Ash
No, no, that was just for Ash.
I don't even support West Ham.
我又没支持西汉姆 他们都被降级了
They were relegated! Oi, they
weren't relegated in that way.
喂 他们可不是因为不行被降级的
So how many ways are there?
That's what a lot of people think,
you see, that West Ham went down
还有其他原因吗
人们普遍认为西汉姆落寞
因为他们水平不行了
但这不是真的
because they weren't any good,
but that's not true.
他们在英冠联只是休息一下
No, no, we just went in the
Championship for a rest, right?
在进军下届英超前 养精蓄锐
To take a break before we launched
our next assault on the Premiership.
So should I say it or not?
Well, Eddie is stubborn remember.
- 那我到底说不说
- 别忘了Eddie可是个老顽固
你就说利物浦队是世界上最好的球队
Just tell him that Liverpool are the
greatest team on the planet. Yes,
he would definitely go for that.
对 他绝对开心
等他开心了 跟你握手的时候
再说Ash给他一个口信
And when he's gone for that and
shaken hands, give him a message
from Ash. Yeah? What's that?
是哦 什么口信
告诉他利物浦队的都是一群娘们
西汉姆才是欧洲第一的
Liverpool play like girls and
West Ham are the only proper team
in Europe. That's not going to help.
- 那可帮不上忙
- 但事实如此
It is true, honestly.
好吧...
All right... Sean, it is
very kind of you to do this,
Sean 谢谢你自告奋勇 我们继续吧
but let's move on.
明天9点 Emma去敲定细节
Tomorrow, at nine, Emma sets up
the mark. Ash, make sure the bars
are in place.
Ash 你确保金条就位
还有 记住 我们要让他确信
And remember, we need to make sure
this guy believes that this is just
a deal that's gone wrong,
是交易遇到了麻烦 而不是骗局
not that he's been conned. OK?
Albert和我会想办法来个干净的收尾
So Albert and I will work out
a way of blowing him out clean.
车上见 不见不散
Meet you at my car.
I'll see you there.
You all right?
你还好吧
Well?
怎么说
货验好了吧
I assume it all checked out.
好货
Good as gold.
So we have a deal?
- 可以交易了吧
- 何时何地
When and where?
和上次一样 高速公路下
Under the motorway,
same as last time.
一小时以后
One hour.
- 你最后快点联系买家
- 好的
You'd better get on to your buyer.
All right.
Shania
Shania!
给Heinz拨电话 快点
Get Heinz on the phone. Now!
PHONE RINGS
Heinz 好消息 我们敲定了
Heinz! Happy days, we're on.
Barry会带你去交易地点
你跟在我后面就好了
Barry will bring you to the meeting
point, stick behind us in my car.
- 我会到
- 带上你的支票簿
I'll be there.
Bring your cheque book.
大家好啊
All right?
- 准备好了?
- 当然
You ready? Oh, yeah.
Well, let's get on with it then.
那就开始吧
除非你想让一个50人的特遣队
跑来毁了我们的派对
Unless you want a 50-strong
special ops unit dropping in
to spoil the party.
He's setting us up!
我们中计了
没事 没事 他们是跟我一起的
Whoa! Whoa! No! No, they're with me!
No! It's all right! It's all good!
没事的
一切正常 他们跟我一起的
It's good as gold. No, see,
they're with me.
他是我跟班 Barry 他把买家带来了
That's my lad, Barry.
He's brought my buyer. See,
I'm the middle man, he's the buyer.
我是中间人 他是买家
他付我钱 我再付给你
是这样的 对吧
He pays me, I pay you,
that's how it works. OK?
- 你想怎么样
- 验货
What do you need? See the gold.
额 我们得验下货
Er, we need to see the goods.
Sir?
长官
你一定会喜欢的 Heinz
You'll like this, Heinz.
我验过样品了
I verified the gold.
See? Everyone's happy!
看 皆大欢喜吧
没事的 做生意嘛 就这样
It's all good.
it's just business, that's all.
站住 你退下 叫他退下
Freeze! Yo, back up!
Tell him to back up!
好好好 我现在转账给你
It's OK! I'm going to pay you now.
好吧
HE CHUCKLES
RUMBLING SOUND
They're on to us!
他们是来抓我们的
你丫差点害我们被宰了
You nearly got us bloody killed.
希望下次交易不会那么戏剧化
I hope our next delivery
is not quite so eventful.
是啊 很抱歉 Heinz
但我们都没事 对吧
Yeah, sorry about that, Heinz.
But all's well and all that, yeah?
再接再励哈
Chin up!
Auf wiedersehen!
再会
好了 回办公室看看广告做得怎样了
Right. Get back to the office,
see how them ads are doing.
Can't I come back with you?
我不能和你一起回去吗
不行 我还有事
看 那儿有个巴士站
No you can't, I've got things to do.
Look, there's a bus stop over there.
抱歉 先生 关门了
Sorry, sir. Closed.
What do you mean it's closed?
It's one o'clock!
关门是什么意思 现在才一点
我要兑现汇票
I've got a bankers' draft to cash.
The bank ceased trading at 11.30
this morning, sir. What!?
银行今早11:30就停止交易了 先生
- 什么
- 具体的我不清楚 先生
I'm not sure of the details, sir,
but the bank's assets have been
seized and all trading suspended.
但银行的资产被扣押了
所有交易暂停
可是... 可是... 我有...
我有一张银行汇票要兑
But... But... I've got a...
I've got a bankers draft!
在这 看 银行汇票
Here! Look! It's a bank draft!
看到了吧 他们得付钱
See! They have to pay it!
如我所说 很抱歉 先生
所有交易暂停
Like I said, I'm sorry, sir,
but all trading has been suspended.
- 银行汇票或直接汇款
- 同意
Bankers draft or direct transfers.
Agreed.
看来你找到你的英国供货商了
Looks like you've found
your UK supplier.
很好 我这位朋友有两张进靶场的票
Good. A friend got two tickets for
the archery, he was hacked off - he
didn't know they did archery there.
他很不爽 不知道他们有在那训练
He said it would've been all right,
though. Excuse me for just a moment.
但他说没事的 他更...
- 抱歉失陪一会
- 随意
Sure. Sorry.
- 很抱歉
-
You talked the talk,
it's time to walk the walk.
There's three mill's worth here,
are you in or are you out?
OK, we have a deal.
好 成交 我全要了
I'll take them all.
很好 再联系
Good call. Be in touch.
手续上我来搞定
但问题是你能不能拿下
I can do the paperwork,
but can you handle it?
不能光说不练啊
You've talked the talk,
it's time to walk the walk.
值三百万呢 你到底要不要
There's three mill's worth here,
are you in or out?
好 成交
OK, we have a deal.
I'll take them all. Good call.
- 我全要了
- 很好 再联系
Be in touch.
一如既往的精彩
As brilliant as ever you were.
谢谢 Paul
Thank you, Paul.
Shania
Shania!
马上打给Heinz
Get Heinz on the phone. Now!
PHONE RINGS
Mm-hmm.
- 嗯
- Heinz 美好的一天啊
'Heinz! Happy days!
交易成了
'We're on!'
我会去的
I'll be there.
没事的 看 皆大欢喜
It's all good.
See? Everyone's happy!
我最好还是把它们给融了
I'd better get this
melted back down.
噢 但...这个融不得
Ah, but... Not this one.
你 呃...你确定没错哈
You, eh...
you sure that's the right one?
- 谢谢
- 你们的话 随时乐意效劳
Thank you.
For you guys, any time.
我知道你们能耐大
但搞来军队 怎么做到的
I knew you were good
but getting the army onside?
How did that work?
Can I ask why you're selling?
能问下你干吗要卖了这里呢
There's an army base
half a mile away,
半里外有个军队基地
他们本该在下一块地演练的
they're meant to do their manoeuvres
in the next field.
但他们老迷路 结果就跑我农场上来了
But they keep getting lost
and ending up on my farm.
逢星期二 星期六中午
跟钟一样准时
Every Tuesday and Saturday at noon.
Just like clockwork.
ALARM BLEEPS
- 商业机密
- 告诉你就得灭你口了
Trade secret.
We could tell you
but we'd have to kill you.
敢情好
Fair enough.
我们要改印铅 但一分都没少
We had to change the seal
but it's all there.
- 完了
- 还好吧
It's done. All right?
Let's get rid of Heinz's phone.
让我们解决掉Heinz的手机
嗨 这送给你
Hi. This is for you.
PHONE RINGS
Hello?
喂
你的支票兑不了 你偷了我的金子
Your cheque's no good!
You nicked my gold!
Who is that?
是谁啊
是Norman
It's Norman.
宝宝乖 排排坐 吃果果
'Cock-a-doodle-doo.'
喂
'Hello?'
'Hello!'
喂
'Hello?!'
Eddie那解决了吗
So Eddie's all sorted?
Like it never happened.
和好如初了
所以 你向他道歉
然后大夸利物浦队 他就信了吗
So what, you apologised, bigged up
Liverpool and he swallowed it?
没错
Yeah.
他没提到我名字吗
He didn't mention my name?
Let's just say it's forgotten.
已经成为过去式了
就这样
Just like that?
我当然得施展魅力 说服他
但他人很好
I had to use charm, talk him round.
But yeah, he's sweet.
我们可以回去了咯
So we can go back in?
Whenever we like. Well done, Sean.
- 随时
- 干得好 Sean
- 绝对的
- 谢了
Absolutely. Thank you.
WOMAN SOBS
你到底跟他说了什么
So what did you say to him exactly?
Well...
这个嘛...
It was Ash. Knew it!
- 是Ash干的
- 我就知道
So where is he then?
他在哪
算了吧 你知道他的 他很高傲
Come on, you know him.
He's a proud man.
- 我要他道歉
- 他也想道歉的
I want an apology.
And he wants to apologise.
他只是不能鼓起勇气当面跟你道歉
He just can't bring himself
to do it face-to-face.
所以他给了我这个
So he gave me this.
Ash的口信
'A message from Ash.
很抱歉 我毁了有史以来
最伟大球员的照片
'I'm sorry for defacing
the photograph
'of the greatest footballer
who ever lived. Ian Rush.'
Ian Rush
伙计们 很多人认为西汉姆联队没落
Many people think West Ham went down
cos they weren't any good
but that's not true.
是因为他们水平不行
事实上不是的
绝对不是 我们只是想
在英冠联休息一下
No, no. We just went into
the Championship for a rest, right,
可以冲击下一届英超
to take a break before we launched
our next assault on the Premiership.
那我到底该不该说呢
So should I say it or not?
告诉他利物浦队是世界上最好的球队
Tell him Liverpool
are the best team on the planet.
这句话他肯定受用
He would definitely go for that.
当他软化时 跟他握手 告诉他
After that and you've shaken hands,
give him a message.
啊 说什么
Yeah? What's that?
利物浦就像一群娘们在踢球
西汉姆联队是欧洲唯一好的球队
Liverpool play like girls
and West Ham are the only
proper team in Europe.
利物浦是欧洲唯一好的球队
'Liverpool are the only proper team
in Europe.'
(Brilliant!)
老实说 西汉姆联队衰落就是实力不好
'Let's be honest. West Ham went down
because they weren't good enough.
利物浦是世界上最好的球队
'Liverpool are the best team
on the planet.
西汉姆联队就像是一群娘们在踢球
利物浦是欧洲唯一一支好的球队
'West Ham play like a load of girls
'and Liverpool are the only
proper team in Europe.'
没事了吧
So we're good?
Come here.
过来
我基本按照你教的说来着
I pretty much told him
exactly what you told me to.
可能没有字字精确 但你知道的
I mean, I might not have got it
word for word, but you know.
- 主要意思都说清了吧
- 哦 当然 当然
But you gave him the gist?
Oh, yeah. Yeah, yeah.
那是位快乐的女士
That is a very happy lady.
So what did you tell her?
你跟她说了什么
我告诉他我是监察专员
她能得到损害赔偿金了
I told her I was an ombudsman
and she'd just been awarded damages.
做得好
A very sweet thing for you to do.
- 也多亏了你们的帮助
- 随时
Well, thank you all for your help.
Any time.
好消息是 我们可以回Eddie那了
And the good news is,
we can go back to Eddie's.
- 噢
- 没错 Sean的功劳
Oh?
Yeah, Sean did the business.
既然这样 那我们还等什么
Well, what are we waiting for?
伙计们 很高兴见到你们 快进来吧
Guys! Good to see you, come on in.
- 那我们没事吧 恩
- 一笔勾销了 无需多说
So we're OK? Eh?
All forgotten, not another word.
Bottle of bubbly on ice,
waiting for you. On the house.
一瓶冰镇香槟在等了 我请
- 谢谢 Eddie
- 耶 Eddie
Thank you, Eddie!
Cheers, Eddie. It's OK.
Oh.
哦
还好吧 Ed
All right, Ed?
You're a top man, Ash,
you know that?
你很棒 Ash 你知道吗
承认错误不容易的
It's not easy
admitting you're wrong.
不 不 你过奖了
No, no, it can't have been.
- 要极具勇气才能迈出这么一步
- 是的 没错
Takes a big man to step up
to the plate. Yes, it does.
Any chance of you letting go now?
- 你能让我走了吗
- 抱歉
Sorry.
听着 我知道你不喜欢我小题大做
但我想让你知道...
Look, I know
you don't like any fuss
but I just want you to know, that...
作为一个男人...我敬重你
I respect you...as a man.
作为个男人 我也敬重你 Ed
And I respect you too, Ed.
As a man.
我知道的 我知道的
I know you do. I know you do.
就这样 都成过眼云烟了 无须多言
So that's it then, yeah, water under
the bridge, not another word? Right.
没错
Right.
- 好了 我们能开酒了吗
- 可以 可以
Right, shall we open the bottle, or?
Yes, yes.
MICKEY LAUGHS
OK, now.
好了
这...献给我们金灿灿的未来
This...is to a golden future.
没想到会再见到我吧
Bet you never thought
you'd see me again.
退下 下士
Back off, corporal.
是的 没想到
No, we didn't.
你带我去仓库时
我听到了你们的对话
Only when you were taking me
into the barn, I heard you talking.
Eddie又不是伦敦唯一一家酒吧
Eddie's isn't the only bar
in London.
或许我们能另找个地方
Maybe we should just find
somewhere else.
不 不 总有办法的
No, no,
we'll find a way to sort it.
希望渺茫 但...
It was a bit of a long shot, but...
Tell you the truth, I thought
you'd be long gone by now.
不得不说 我以为
你们可能已经消失了
The thing is...
问题是...
那五十万磅把我给毁了
有人要付出代价
..that half a million quid broke me
and someone's got to pay.
你想怎样
So...what do you have in mind?
别急
ASH: Relax.
听着 我没想找你们晦气
Look, I haven't got any beef
with you guys.
- 什么- 你们拿了我的钱
那是生意 我能理解
Sorry?
OK, you got my money, but that was
business. I understand that.
I got the gold,
I gave it to Heinz, I took a hit.
我拿到金块 转卖给Heinz 赚个差价
你们得到应得的 我毫无怨言
You kept to your end of the bargain,
I've got no complaints about that.
但那德国佬骗了我
But that Kraut cheated me!
他拿走了金砖 给我不能用的支票
现在我找不到他了
He took my gold and he gave me a
dodgy cheque, now I can't find him.
His office number's unavailable
他办公室电话打不通
手机又被某个疯子偷了
and some nutcase
has nicked his mobile.
这有五千
50 grand.
Now, I know you lot
were Black Ops in the army,
我知道你们有军事背景
so I thought who better
to help me out.
所以我想找你们帮忙
- 黑色行动
- 没关系 我知道你们不能声张
Black Ops?
It's OK.
I know you can't talk about it.
但我懂的
But I know how it works.
我知道你们做什么的
I know what you do.
What's that, then?
那是什么呢
你们深入敌后 先发制人
You get dropped behind enemy lines
to take people out.
Well, that's what I want you to do
to the German.
我也正想要你们这么对付那德国佬
把他挖出来
I want you to track him down for me.
His name is Heinz Zimmerman.
他叫Heinz Zimmerman
找到他 然后帮我好好照料他
I want you to find him,
and I want you to...
take care of him for me.
- "好好照料他"
- 你们懂的
"Take care of him?"
You know what I mean.
噢 对 好好照料他
Oh, yeah. Take care of him.
这一共五万磅
把他带给我后再给五万磅
There's 50 grand there,
there'll be the same again
when you bring him to me.
或给我看...
他死后冰冷尸体的照片
Or show me a photo...
of his cold, dead body.
做不做
Do we have a deal?
Let me get this straight.
让我把话说白了
是不是我们找到Heinz Zimmerman
解决掉他
If we find this Heinz Zimmerman,
take care of him,
给出照片证明 你会再给我们五万
and show you a photo of that,
you'll give us another 50 thousand?
没错
That's right.
Then you've got a deal.
成交
你知道怎么联系我的
You know where to find me.
这不是真的吧
Did that just happen?
- 没错 是真的
- 刚我还以为我们有麻烦了
Yes, it did. I thought we were
in trouble for a minute.
不用担心 我搞定
Not to worry, I'm on it.
Wait a minute.
等等
呃 一定要在衬衫上撒番茄酱吗
Ugh, did you have to put ketchup
on this shirt?
With five grand, you can buy a new
shirt. You have to look the part.
五千磅可以买件新的了
你总得看着像回事啊
就是装死
Or dead to be precise.
知道 不 抓那里 抓那儿
OK, now, that. No.
Hold that, hold that.
太好了
That's fantastic.
I really missed you lot, you know.
我想死你们了 知道吗
是吗 我们也很想你 Ed
Yeah, well, we missed you too, Ed.
- 真的吗
- 是啊 别再抱我了
Did you?
Yeah. Just don't hug me again.
为西汉姆联队干杯
Here's to West Ham.
哦 干杯
Oh, cheers.
Hang on a minute, you're supposed
to say, "Here's to Liverpool."
等等 你应该说 "为利物浦队干杯"
为什么
What for?
噢 这太不对了吧
Well, that's not very nice, is it?
你继续这样 那道歉还有什么意义
What's the point in apologising
if you behave like that?
但道歉的是Sean 我没有啊
But Sean apologised, I didn't.
- 有 你有
- 不 我什么也没干
Yes, you did.
No, I didn't do anything.
那张CD呢
What about the CD?
什么CD
What CD?
Ash的口信
'Message from Ash.
很抱歉我损坏了有史以来
最伟大球员的照片
'I'm sorry for defacing
the photograph
'of the greatest footballer
who ever lived. Ian Rush.'
Ian Rush
Ash...这我可以解释
Ash...
This...
this can be easily explained.
收一份钱 杀两个人怎样
How about two dead bodies
for the price of one.
不过一个是真死...
Only one of 'em will be real...
因为我要杀了你
..cos I'm going to kill you.
- Ash
- Sean 赶紧跑
Ash. Sean, just run.
别傻站了 快帮我
Don't just stand there! Help me!
Ash 别逼我做后悔的事
Ash, don't make me do something
I'm going to regret!
Argh!
太紧了 太紧了 Ash
That's pretty tight.
That's pretty tight! Ash!
FRS时间轴招聘群号：37304379
FRM字幕组招聘邮箱：frzhaopin2@gmail.com
与最新美剧亲密接触 享受海量FTP下载
风软FRM字幕组作品
-==http://www.1000fr.net==-
欢迎加入
Subtitles by Red Bee Media Ltd
E-mail subtitling@bbc.co.uk